[
  {
    "question": "Question #2 Topic 1\nYour company has datacenters in Los Angeles and New York. The company has a Microsoft Azure subscription.\nYou are con\u0000guring the two datacenters as geo-clustered sites for site resiliency.\nYou need to recommend an Azure storage redundancy option.\nYou have the following data storage requirements:\n Data must be stored on multiple nodes.\n Data must be stored on nodes in separate geographic locations.\n Data can be read from the secondary location as well as from the primary location\nWhich of the following Azure stored redundancy options should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Geo-redundant storage",
      "B": "Read-only geo-redundant storage",
      "C": "Zone-redundant storage",
      "D": "Locally redundant storage"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #3 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's Azure subscription includes a Basic support plan.\nThey would like to request an assessment of an Azure environment's design from Microsoft. This is, however, not supported by the existing\nplan.\nYou want to make sure that the company subscribes to a support plan that allows this functionality, while keeping expenses to a minimum.\nSolution: You recommend that the company subscribes to the Professional Direct support plan.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #4 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.\nYou need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Software as a Service (SaaS).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #5 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.\nYou need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Platform as a Service (PaaS).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #6 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.\nYou need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #7 Topic 1\nYour developers have created 10 web applications that must be host on Azure.\nYou need to determine which Azure web tier plan to host the web apps. The web tier plan must meet the following requirements:\n The web apps will use custom domains.\n The web apps each require 10 GB of storage.\n The web apps must each run in dedicated compute instances.\n Load balancing between instances must be included.\n Costs must be minimized.\nWhich web tier plan should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Standard",
      "B": "Basic",
      "C": "Free",
      "D": "Shared"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #8 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are planning to migrate a company to Azure. Each of the company's numerous divisions will have an administrator in place to manage the\nAzure resources used by their respective division.\nYou want to make sure that the Azure deployment you employ allows for Azure to be segmented for the divisions, while keeping\nadministrative effort to a minimum.\nSolution: You plan to make use of several Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) directories.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #9 Topic 1\nYour developers have created a portal web app for users in the Miami branch o\u0000ce. The web app will be publicly accessible and used by the\nMiami users to retrieve customer and product information. The web app is currently running in an on-premises test environment.\nYou plan to host the web app on Azure.\nYou need to determine which Azure web tier plan to host the web app. The web tier plan must meet the following requirements:\n The website will use the miami.weyland.com URL.\n The website will be deployed to two instances.\n SSL support must be included.\n The website requires 12 GB of storage.\n Costs must be minimized.\nWhich web tier plan should you use?",
    "options": {
      "L": "The website will be deployed to two instances.\n SSL support must be included.\n The website requires 12 GB of storage.\n Costs must be minimized.\nWhich web tier plan should you use?",
      "A": "Standard",
      "B": "Basic",
      "C": "Free",
      "D": "Shared"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #10 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently\nhosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.\nSolution: You should recommend the use of the elastic expenditure model.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #11 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently\nhosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.\nSolution: You should recommend the use of the scalable expenditure model.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #12 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently\nhosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.\nSolution: You should recommend the use of the operational expenditure model.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #13 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are required to deploy an Arti\u0000cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.\nYou want to make sure that you are able to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics for the solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Azure Cosmos DB.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "B": "No",
      "A": "Yes"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #14 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's Active Directory forest includes thousands of user accounts.\nYou have been informed that all network resources will be migrated to Azure. Thereafter, the on-premises data center will be retired.\nYou are required to employ a strategy that reduces the effect on users, once the planned migration has been completed.\nSolution: You plan to sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #15 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are required to deploy an Arti\u0000cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.\nYou want to make sure that you are able to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics for the solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Azure Machine Learning Studio.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #16 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everyday\noperation.\nThe resources required by each business unit are identical.\nYou are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.\nSolution: You recommend that the Azure API Management service be included in the strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #17 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everyday\noperation.\nThe resources required by each business unit are identical.\nYou are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.\nSolution: You recommend that management groups be included in the strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #18 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everyday\noperation.\nThe resources required by each business unit are identical.\nYou are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.\nSolution: You recommend that the Azure Resource Manager templates be included in the strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #19 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.\nYou are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure\nthat the strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.\nSolution: You include two virtual machines and one availability zone in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #20 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.\nYou are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure\nthat the strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.\nSolution: You include one virtual machine and two availability zones in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #21 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.\nYou are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure\nthat the strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.\nSolution: You include two virtual machines and two availability zones in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #22 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing these\nvirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the\nother forty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.\nYou are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Microsoft Managed Desktop.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #23 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing these\nvirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the\nother forty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.\nYou are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure Reserved Virtual Machines (VM) Instances.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #24 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing these\nvirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the\nother forty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.\nYou are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure DevTest Labs.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #25 Topic 1\nYour company has virtual machines (VMs) hosted in Microsoft Azure. The VMs are located in a single Azure virtual network named VNet1.\nThe company has users that work remotely. The remote workers require access to the VMs on VNet1.\nYou need to provide access for the remote workers.\nWhat should you do?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Con\u0000gure a Site-to-Site (S2S) VPN.",
      "B": "Con\u0000gure a VNet-toVNet VPN.",
      "C": "Con\u0000gure a Point-to-Site (P2S) VPN.",
      "D": "Con\u0000gure DirectAccess on a Windows Server 2012 server VM.",
      "E": "Con\u0000gure a Multi-Site VPN"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #26 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou have been informed by your superiors of the company's intentions to automate server deployment to Azure. There is, however, some\nconcern that administrative credentials could be uncovered during this process.\nYou are required to make sure that during the deployment, the administrative credentials are encrypted using a suitable Azure solution.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure Information Protection.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #27 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou have been informed by your superiors of the company's intentions to automate server deployment to Azure. There is, however, some\nconcern that administrative credentials could be uncovered during this process.\nYou are required to make sure that during the deployment, the administrative credentials are encrypted using a suitable Azure solution.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #29 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) environment. Users occasionally connect to Azure AD via the Internet.\nYou have been tasked with making sure that users who connect to Azure AD via the internet from an unidenti\u0000ed IP address, are automatically\nencouraged to change passwords.\nSolution: You con\u0000gure the use of Azure AD Identity Protection.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #30 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) environment. Users occasionally connect to Azure AD via the Internet.\nYou have been tasked with making sure that users who connect to Azure AD via the internet from an unidenti\u0000ed IP address, are automatically\nencouraged to change passwords.\nSolution: You con\u0000gure the use of Azure AD Privileged Identity Management.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #31 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are planning a strategy to deploy numerous web servers and database servers to Azure.\nThis strategy should allow for connection types between the web servers and database servers to be controlled.\nSolution: You include network security groups (NSGs) in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #32 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYou are planning a strategy to deploy numerous web servers and database servers to Azure.\nThis strategy should allow for connection types between the web servers and database servers to be controlled.\nSolution: You include a local network gateway in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #33 Topic 1\nNote: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis\u0000es the requirements.\nYour company's Active Directory forest includes thousands of user accounts.\nYou have been informed that all network resources will be migrated to Azure. Thereafter, the on-premises data center will be retired.\nYou are required to employ a strategy that reduces the effect on users, once the planned migration has been completed.\nSolution: You plan to require Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #37 Topic 1\nYou have an on-premises network that contains several servers.\nYou plan to migrate all the servers to Azure.\nYou need to recommend a solution to ensure that some of the servers are available if a single Azure data center goes o\u0000ine for an extended\nperiod.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "fault tolerance",
      "B": "elasticity",
      "C": "scalability",
      "D": "low latency"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #39 Topic 1\nWhat are two characteristics of the public cloud? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "dedicated hardware",
      "B": "unsecured connections",
      "C": "limited storage",
      "D": "metered pricing",
      "E": "self-service management"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #41 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #42 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure virtual machines that have Microsoft SQL Server installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #43 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure Storage accounts.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #44 Topic 1\nYour company hosts an accounting application named App1 that is used by all the customers of the company.\nApp1 has low usage during the \u0000rst three weeks of each month and very high usage during the last week of each month.\nWhich bene\u0000t of Azure Cloud Services supports cost management for this type of usage pattern?",
    "options": {
      "A": "high availability",
      "B": "high latency",
      "C": "elasticity",
      "D": "load balancing"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #45 Topic 1\nYou plan to migrate a web application to Azure. The web application is accessed by external users.\nYou need to recommend a cloud deployment solution to minimize the amount of administrative effort used to manage the web application.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Software as a Service (SaaS)",
      "B": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
      "C": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)",
      "D": "Database as a Service (DaaS)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #47 Topic 1\nYou have an on-premises network that contains 100 servers.\nYou need to recommend a solution that provides additional resources to your users. The solution must minimize capital and operational\nexpenditure costs.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a complete migration to the public cloud",
      "B": "an additional data center",
      "C": "a private cloud",
      "D": "a hybrid cloud"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #49 Topic 1\nYou plan to migrate several servers from an on-premises network to Azure.\nWhat is an advantage of using a public cloud service for the servers over an on-premises network?",
    "options": {
      "A": "The public cloud is owned by the public, NOT a private corporation",
      "B": "The public cloud is a crowd-sourcing solution that provides corporations with the ability to enhance the cloud",
      "C": "All public cloud resources can be freely accessed by every member of the public",
      "D": "The public cloud is a shared entity whereby multiple corporations each use a portion of the resources in the cloud"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #51 Topic 1\nIn which type of cloud model are all the hardware resources owned by a third-party and shared between multiple tenants?",
    "options": {
      "A": "private",
      "B": "hybrid",
      "C": "public"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #53 Topic 1\nYou have 1,000 virtual machines hosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou plan to migrate all the virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription.\nYou need to identify which expenditure model to use for the planned Azure solution.\nWhich expenditure model should you identify?",
    "options": {
      "A": "operational",
      "B": "elastic",
      "C": "capital",
      "D": "scalable"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #57 Topic 1\nYour company has an on-premises network that contains multiple servers.\nThe company plans to reduce the following administrative responsibilities:\n Backing up application data\n Replacing failed server hardware\n Managing physical server security\n Updating server operating systems\n Managing permissions to shared documents\nThe company plans to migrate servers to Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to identify which administrative responsibilities will be eliminated after the planned migration.\nWhich two responsibilities should you identify? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Replacing failed server hardware",
      "B": "Backing up application data",
      "C": "Managing physical server security",
      "D": "Updating server operating systems",
      "E": "Managing permissions to shared documents"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #59 Topic 1\nYou plan to provision Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) resources in Azure.\nWhich resource is an example of IaaS?",
    "options": {
      "A": "an Azure web app",
      "B": "an Azure virtual machine",
      "C": "an Azure logic app",
      "D": "an Azure SQL database"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #60 Topic 1\nTo which cloud models can you deploy physical servers?",
    "options": {
      "A": "private cloud and hybrid cloud only",
      "B": "private cloud only",
      "C": "private cloud, hybrid cloud and public cloud",
      "D": "hybrid cloud only"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #63 Topic 1\nYou have 50 virtual machines hosted on-premises and 50 virtual machines hosted in Azure. The on-premises virtual machines and the Azure\nvirtual machines connect to each other.\nWhich type of cloud model is this?",
    "options": {
      "A": "hybrid",
      "B": "private",
      "C": "public"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #65 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create Azure virtual machines, Azure SQL databases, and Azure Storage accounts.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #66 Topic 1\nYour company plans to deploy several custom applications to Azure. The applications will provide invoicing services to the customers of the\ncompany. Each application will have several prerequisite applications and services installed.\nYou need to recommend a cloud deployment solution for all the applications.\nWhat should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Software as a Service (SaaS)",
      "B": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
      "C": "Infrastructure as a Service (laaS)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #73 Topic 1\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company's migration plan.\nWhat should you create?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure virtual machines, Azure SQL databases, and Azure Storage accounts.",
      "B": "an Azure App Service and Azure virtual machines that have Microsoft SQL Server installed.",
      "C": "an Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases.",
      "D": "Azure storage accounts and web server in Azure virtual machines."
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #74 Topic 1\nWhat does a customer provide in a software as a service (SaaS) model?",
    "options": {
      "A": "application data",
      "B": "data storage",
      "C": "compute resources",
      "D": "application software"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #77 Topic 1\nWhat is the \u0000rst stage in the Microsoft Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Adopt the cloud.",
      "B": "Make a plan.",
      "C": "Ready your organization.",
      "D": "De\u0000ne your strategy."
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #83 Topic 1\nYou have an accounting application named App1 that uses a legacy database.\nYou plan to move App1 to the cloud.\nWhich service model should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "platform as a service (PaaS)",
      "B": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)",
      "C": "software as a service (SaaS)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #87 Topic 1\nWhich cloud computing model includes on-premises and cloud-based resources?",
    "options": {
      "A": "hybrid",
      "B": "public",
      "C": "private"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #90 Topic 1\nWhich term represents the ability to increase the computing capacity of a virtual machine by adding memory or CPUs?",
    "options": {
      "A": "agility",
      "B": "vertical scaling",
      "C": "horizontal scaling",
      "D": "elasticity"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #91 Topic 1\nWhat are two bene\u0000ts of cloud computing? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "enables the rapid provisioning of resources",
      "B": "has increased administrative complexity",
      "C": "has the same con\u0000guration options as on-premises",
      "D": "shifts capital expenditures (CAPEX) to operating expenditures (OPEX)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #92 Topic 1\nWhat is a feature of an Azure virtual network?",
    "options": {
      "A": "resource cost analysis",
      "B": "packet inspection",
      "C": "geo-redundancy",
      "D": "isolation and segmentation"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #95 Topic 1\nWhich cloud computing bene\u0000t provides continuous user access to a cloud-based application with minimal downtime?",
    "options": {
      "A": "agility",
      "B": "scalability",
      "C": "elasticity",
      "D": "high availability"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #96 Topic 1\nYou need to identify the type of failure for which an Azure Availability Zone can be used to protect access to Azure services.\nWhat should you identify?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a physical server failure",
      "B": "an Azure region failure",
      "C": "a storage failure",
      "D": "an Azure data center failure"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #98 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more resource groups.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #99 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to a scale set.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #101 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nResource groups provide organizations with the ability to manage the compliance of Azure resources across multiple subscriptions.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed",
      "B": "Management groups",
      "C": "Azure policies",
      "D": "Azure App Service plans"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #102 Topic 1\nYour company plans to migrate to Azure.\nThe company has several departments. All the Azure resources used by each department will be managed by a department administrator.\nWhat are two possible techniques to segment Azure for the departments? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "multiple subscriptions",
      "B": "multiple Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) directories",
      "C": "multiple regions",
      "D": "multiple resource groups"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #105 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure environment that contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou plan to implement a solution that enables the client computers on your on-premises network to communicate to the Azure virtual\nmachines.\nYou need to recommend which Azure resources must be created for the planned solution.\nWhich two Azure resources should you include in the recommendation? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "a virtual network gateway",
      "B": "a load balancer",
      "C": "an application gateway",
      "D": "a virtual network",
      "E": "a gateway subnet"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #106 Topic 1\nYou attempt to create several managed Microsoft SQL Server instances in an Azure environment and receive a message that you must\nincrease your Azure subscription limits.\nWhat should you do to increase the limits?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Create a service health alert",
      "B": "Upgrade your support plan",
      "C": "Modify an Azure policy",
      "D": "Create a new support request"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #110 Topic 1\nYour company plans to move several servers to Azure.\nThe company's compliance policy states that a server named FinServer must be on a separate network segment.\nYou are evaluating which Azure services can be used to meet the compliance policy requirements.\nWhich Azure solution should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a resource group for FinServer and another resource group for all the other servers",
      "B": "a virtual network for FinServer and another virtual network for all the other servers",
      "C": "a VPN for FinServer and a virtual network gateway for each other server",
      "D": "one resource group for all the servers and a resource lock for FinServer"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #111 Topic 1\nYou plan to map a network drive from several computers that run Windows 10 to Azure Storage.\nYou need to create a storage solution in Azure for the planned mapped drive.\nWhat should you create?",
    "options": {
      "A": "an Azure SQL database",
      "B": "a virtual machine data disk",
      "C": "a File service in a storage account",
      "D": "a Blob service in a storage account"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #113 Topic 1\nYour company plans to start using Azure and will migrate all its network resources to Azure.\nYou need to start the planning process by exploring Azure.\nWhat should you create \u0000rst?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a subscription",
      "B": "a resource group",
      "C": "a virtual network",
      "D": "a management group"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #117 Topic 1\nWhich Azure service should you use to collect events from multiple resources into a centralized repository?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Event Hubs",
      "B": "Azure Analysis Services",
      "C": "Azure Monitor",
      "D": "Azure Stream Analytics"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #122 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more scale sets.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #123 Topic 1\nYou need to be noti\u0000ed when Microsoft plans to perform maintenance that can affect the resources deployed to an Azure subscription.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Monitor",
      "B": "Azure Service Health",
      "C": "Azure Advisor",
      "D": "Microsoft Trust Center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #131 Topic 1\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines remain available if a single data center fails.\nWhat are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more availability zones.",
      "B": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more resource groups.",
      "C": "Deploy the virtual machines to a scale set.",
      "D": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more regions."
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #135 Topic 1\nWhat is the most severe failure from which an Azure Availability Zone can be used to protect access to Azure service?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a physical server failure",
      "B": "an Azure region failure",
      "C": "a storage failure",
      "D": "an Azure data center failure"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #136 Topic 1\nYou need to purchase a third-party virtual security appliance that you will deploy to an Azure subscription.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure subscriptions",
      "B": "Azure Security Center",
      "C": "Azure Marketplace",
      "D": "Microsoft Store"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #142 Topic 1\nYou need to purchase a third-party virtual security appliance that you will deploy to an Azure subscription.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure subscriptions",
      "B": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud",
      "C": "Azure Marketplace",
      "D": "Microsoft Store"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #144 Topic 1\nYou plan to deploy a service to Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the service will be available if a datacenter fails.\nWhat should you use as part of the virtual machine deployment?",
    "options": {
      "A": "availability sets",
      "B": "proximity placement groups",
      "C": "host groups",
      "D": "availability zones"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #145 Topic 1\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains resources in several regions.\nYou need to ensure that administrators can only create resources in those regions.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a read-only lock",
      "B": "an Azure policy",
      "C": "a management group",
      "D": "a reservation"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #148 Topic 1\nWhat is the function of a Site-to-Site VPN?",
    "options": {
      "A": "provides a secure connection between a computer on a public network and the corporate network",
      "B": "provides a dedicated private connection to Azure that does NOT travel over the internet",
      "C": "provides a connection from an on-premises VPN device to an Azure VPN gateway"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #151 Topic 1\nYou need to manage containers.\nWhich two services can you use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Virtual Desktop",
      "B": "Azure virtual machines",
      "C": "Azure Functions",
      "D": "Azure Container Instances",
      "E": "Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #153 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more availability zones.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #154 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nOne of the bene\u0000ts of Azure SQL Data Warehouse is that high availability is built into the platform.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed",
      "B": "automatic scaling",
      "C": "data compression",
      "D": "versioning"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #155 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more regions.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #157 Topic 1\nAt which OSI layer does ExpressRoute operate?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Layer 2",
      "B": "Layer 3",
      "C": "Layer 5",
      "D": "Layer 7"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #160 Topic 1\nYou plan to store 20 TB of data in Azure. The data will be accessed infrequently and visualized by using Microsoft Power BI.\nYou need to recommend a storage solution for the data.\nWhich two solutions should you recommend? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "I": "You need to recommend a storage solution for the data.\nWhich two solutions should you recommend? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "A": "Azure Data Lake",
      "B": "Azure Cosmos DB",
      "C": "Azure SQL Data Warehouse",
      "D": "Azure SQL Database",
      "E": "Azure Database for PostgreSQL"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #164 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con\u0000guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #165 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con\u0000guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #167 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con\u0000guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #172 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use Bash in Azure Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #173 Topic 1\nYou have an on-premises application that sends email noti\u0000cations automatically based on a rule.\nYou plan to migrate the application to Azure.\nYou need to recommend a serverless computing solution for the application.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a web app",
      "B": "a server image in Azure Marketplace",
      "C": "a logic app",
      "D": "an API app"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #174 Topic 1\nYou plan to deploy a website to Azure. The website will be accessed by users worldwide and will host large video \u0000les.\nYou need to recommend which Azure feature must be used to provide the best video playback experience.\nWhat should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "an application gateway",
      "B": "an Azure ExpressRoute circuit",
      "C": "a content delivery network (CDN)",
      "D": "an Azure Tra\u0000c Manager pro\u0000le"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #175 Topic 1\nYour company plans to deploy several million sensors that will upload data to Azure.\nYou need to identify which Azure resources must be created to support the planned solution.\nWhich two Azure resources should you identify? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Data Lake",
      "B": "Azure Queue storage",
      "C": "Azure File Storage",
      "D": "Azure IoT Hub",
      "E": "Azure Noti\u0000cation Hubs"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #176 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure web app.\nYou need to manage the settings of the web app from an iPhone.\nWhat are two Azure management tools that you can use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure CLI",
      "B": "the Azure portal",
      "C": "Azure Cloud Shell",
      "D": "Windows PowerShell",
      "E": "Azure Storage Explorer"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #177 Topic 1\nYour company plans to deploy an Arti\u0000cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.\nWhat should the company use to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics solutions?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Logic Apps",
      "B": "Azure Machine Learning Designer",
      "C": "Azure Batch",
      "D": "Azure Cosmos DB"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #179 Topic 1\nWhat can you use to automatically send an alert if an administrator stops an Azure virtual machine?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Advisor",
      "B": "Azure Service Health",
      "C": "Azure Monitor",
      "D": "Azure Network Watcher"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #181 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure environment.\nYou need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nWhat are three possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Use Bash in Azure Cloud Shell.",
      "B": "Use PowerShell in Azure Cloud Shell.",
      "C": "Use the PowerApps portal.",
      "D": "Use the Security & Compliance admin center.",
      "E": "Use the Azure portal."
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #182 Topic 1\nA team of developers at your company plans to deploy, and then remove, 50 virtual machines each week. All the virtual machines are\ncon\u0000gured by using Azure\nResource Manager templates.\nYou need to recommend which Azure service will minimize the administrative effort required to deploy and remove the virtual machines.\nWhat should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Reserved Virtual Machine (VM) Instances",
      "B": "Azure DevTest Labs",
      "C": "Azure virtual machine scale sets",
      "D": "Azure Virtual Desktop"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #184 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS --generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From the Azure portal, launch Azure Cloud Shell and select PowerShell. Run the command in Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #185 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS\n--generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From a computer that runs Windows 10, install Azure CLI. From PowerShell, sign in to Azure and then run the command.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "I": "From PowerShell, sign in to Azure and then run the command.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #186 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS\n--generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From a computer that runs Windows 10, install Azure CLI. From a command prompt, sign in to Azure and then run the command.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "I": "From a command prompt, sign in to Azure and then run the command.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #191 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con\u0000guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #193 Topic 1\nWhich service provides serverless computing in Azure?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Virtual Machines",
      "B": "Azure Functions",
      "C": "Azure storage account",
      "D": "Azure dedicated hosts"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #194 Topic 1\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con\u0000guration to use to run the script.\nWhich three computers can run the script? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed.",
      "B": "a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed.",
      "C": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure PowerShell module installed.",
      "D": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed.",
      "E": "a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell."
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #195 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS --generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From the Azure portal, launch Azure Cloud Shell and select Bash. Run the command in Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #196 Topic 1\nYour company has several business units.\nEach business unit requires 20 different Azure resources for daily operation. All the business units require the same type of Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend a solution to automate the creation of the Azure resources.\nWhat should you include in the recommendations?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Resource Manager templates",
      "B": "virtual machine scale sets",
      "C": "the Azure API Management service",
      "D": "management groups"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #198 Topic 1\nWhat can you use to identify underutilized or unused Azure virtual machines?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Advisor",
      "B": "Azure Cost Management + Billing",
      "C": "Azure reservations",
      "D": "Azure Policy"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #203 Topic 1\nA team of developers at your company plans to deploy, and then remove, 50 customized virtual machines each week. Thirty of the virtual\nmachines run Windows\nServer 2016 and 20 of the virtual machines run Ubuntu Linux.\nYou need to recommend which Azure service will minimize the administrative effort required to deploy and remove the virtual machines.\nWhat should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Reserved Virtual Machines (VM) Instances",
      "B": "Azure virtual machine scale sets",
      "C": "Azure DevTest Labs",
      "D": "Microsoft Managed Desktop"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #205 Topic 1\nA support engineer plans to perform several Azure management tasks by using the Azure CLI.\nYou install the CLI on a computer.\nYou need to tell the support engineer which tools to use to run the CLI.\nWhich two tools should you instruct the support engineer to use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "I": "You install the CLI on a computer.\nYou need to tell the support engineer which tools to use to run the CLI.\nWhich two tools should you instruct the support engineer to use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "A": "Command Prompt",
      "B": "Azure Resource Explorer",
      "C": "Windows PowerShell",
      "D": "Windows Defender Firewall",
      "E": "Network and Sharing Center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #206 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use PowerShell in Azure Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #207 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use the PowerApps portal.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #208 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use the Azure portal.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #214 Topic 1\nWhich Azure service provides a set of version control tools to manage code?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Repos",
      "B": "Azure DevTest Labs",
      "C": "Azure Storage",
      "D": "Azure Cosmos DB"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #216 Topic 1\nYou have a virtual machine named VM1 that runs Windows Server 2016. VM1 is in the East US Azure region.\nWhich Azure service should you use from the Azure portal to view service failure noti\u0000cations that can affect the availability of VM1?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Service Fabric",
      "B": "Azure Monitor",
      "C": "Azure virtual machines",
      "D": "Azure Advisor"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #217 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify an Azure Tra\u0000c Manager pro\u0000le.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "P": "Solution: You modify an Azure Tra\u0000c Manager pro\u0000le.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #218 Topic 1\nYour company plans to deploy several web servers and several database servers to Azure.\nYou need to recommend an Azure solution to limit the types of connections from the web servers to the database servers.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "network security groups (NSGs)",
      "B": "Azure Service Bus",
      "C": "a local network gateway",
      "D": "a route \u0000lter"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #220 Topic 1\nWhich service provides network tra\u0000c \u0000ltering across multiple Azure subscriptions and virtual networks?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Firewall",
      "B": "an application security group",
      "C": "Azure DDoS protection",
      "D": "a network security group (NSG)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #221 Topic 1\nWhich Azure service should you use to store certi\u0000cates?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Security Center",
      "B": "an Azure Storage account",
      "C": "Azure Key Vault",
      "D": "Azure Information Protection"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #222 Topic 1\nWhich Azure service can you use as a security information and event management (SIEM) solution?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Analysis Services",
      "B": "Azure Sentinel",
      "C": "Azure Information Protection",
      "D": "Azure Cognitive Services"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #228 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure virtual machine named VM1.\nYou plan to encrypt VM1 by using Azure Disk Encryption.\nWhich Azure resource must you create \u0000rst?",
    "options": {
      "A": "an Azure Storage account",
      "B": "an Azure Key Vault",
      "C": "an Azure Information Protection policy",
      "D": "an Encryption key"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #229 Topic 1\nWhich resources can be used as a source for a Network security group inbound security rule?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Service Tags only",
      "B": "IP Addresses, Service tags and Application security groups",
      "C": "Application security groups only",
      "D": "IP Addresses only"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #233 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure Sentinel workspace.\nYou need to automate responses to threats detected by Azure Sentinel.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "adaptive network hardening in Azure Security Center",
      "B": "Azure Service Health",
      "C": "Azure Monitor workbooks",
      "D": "adaptive application controls in Azure Security Center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #235 Topic 1\nWhich Azure service can you use as a security information and event management (SIEM) solution?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Analysis Services",
      "B": "Microsoft Sentinel",
      "C": "Azure Information Protection",
      "D": "Azure Cognitive Services"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #237 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure subscription.\nYou need to review your secure score.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Monitor",
      "B": "Azure Advisor",
      "C": "Help + support",
      "D": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #240 Topic 1\nYou need to collect and automatically analyze security events from Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Microsoft Sentinel",
      "B": "Azure Synapse Analytics",
      "C": "Azure AD Connect",
      "D": "Azure Key Vault"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #244 Topic 1\nYour company plans to automate the deployment of servers to Azure.\nYour manager is concerned that you may expose administrative credentials during the deployment.\nYou need to recommend an Azure solution that encrypts the administrative credentials during the deployment.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Key Vault",
      "B": "Azure Information Protection",
      "C": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud",
      "D": "Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #248 Topic 1\nYou need to con\u0000gure an Azure solution that meets the following requirements:\n Secures websites from attacks\n Generates reports that contain details of attempted attacks\nWhat should you include in the solution?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Firewall",
      "B": "a network security group (NSG)",
      "C": "Azure Information Protection",
      "D": "DDoS protection"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #250 Topic 1\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nWhat are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "P": "What are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "A": "Modify an Azure Tra\u0000c Manager pro\u0000le",
      "B": "Modify a network security group (NSG)",
      "C": "Modify a DDoS protection plan",
      "D": "Modify an Azure \u0000rewall"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #253 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure environment that contains 10 virtual networks and 100 virtual machines.\nYou need to limit the amount of inbound tra\u0000c to all the Azure virtual networks.\nWhat should you create?",
    "options": {
      "A": "one application security group (ASG)",
      "B": "10 virtual network gateways",
      "C": "10 Azure ExpressRoute circuits",
      "D": "one Azure \u0000rewall"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #254 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nAzure Key Vault is used to store secrets for Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) user accounts.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed",
      "B": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) administrative accounts",
      "C": "Personally Identi\u0000able Information (PII)",
      "D": "server applications"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #255 Topic 1\nYour company plans to automate the deployment of servers to Azure.\nYour manager is concerned that you may expose administrative credentials during the deployment.\nYou need to recommend an Azure solution that encrypts the administrative credentials during the deployment.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Key Vault",
      "B": "Azure Information Protection",
      "C": "Azure Security Center",
      "D": "Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #256 Topic 1\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to control the ports that devices on the Internet can use to access the virtual machines.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a network security group (NSG)",
      "B": "an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) role",
      "C": "an Azure Active Directory group",
      "D": "an Azure key vault"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #259 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify a network security group (NSG).\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "P": "Solution: You modify a network security group (NSG).\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #260 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify a DDoS protection plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "P": "Solution: You modify a DDoS protection plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #261 Topic 1\nYou need to collect and automatically analyze security events from Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Sentinel",
      "B": "Azure Synapse Analytics",
      "C": "Azure AD Connect",
      "D": "Azure Key Vault"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #262 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify an Azure \u0000rewall.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "P": "Solution: You modify an Azure \u0000rewall.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #263 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nAzure Germany can be used by legal residents of Germany only.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "no change is needed",
      "B": "only enterprises that are registered in Germany",
      "C": "only enterprises that purchase their azure licenses from a partner based in Germany",
      "D": "any user or enterprise that requires its data to reside in Germany"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #266 Topic 1\nWhat should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Service Health",
      "B": "Azure Knowledge Center",
      "C": "Azure Security Center",
      "D": "Azure Advisor"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #269 Topic 1\nWhich two types of customers are eligible to use Azure Government to develop a cloud solution? Each correct answer presents a complete\nsolution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "a Canadian government contractor",
      "B": "a European government contractor",
      "C": "a United States government entity",
      "D": "a United States government contractor",
      "E": "a European government entity"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #271 Topic 1\nYou need to ensure that when Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) users connect to Azure AD from the Internet by using an anonymous IP\naddress, the users are prompted automatically to change their password.\nWhich Azure service should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure AD Connect Health",
      "B": "Azure AD Privileged Identity Management",
      "C": "Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP)",
      "D": "Azure AD Identity Protection"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #273 Topic 1\nTo what should an application connect to retrieve security tokens?",
    "options": {
      "A": "an Azure Storage account",
      "B": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)",
      "C": "a certi\u0000cate store",
      "D": "an Azure key vault"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #274 Topic 1\nYour network contains an Active Directory forest. The forest contains 5,000 user accounts.\nYour company plans to migrate all network resources to Azure and to decommission the on-premises data center.\nYou need to recommend a solution to minimize the impact on users after the planned migration.\nWhat should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Implement Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)",
      "B": "Sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)",
      "C": "Instruct all users to change their password",
      "D": "Create a guest user account in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) for each user"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #277 Topic 1\nYou have a resource group named RG1.\nYou need to prevent the creation of virtual machines in RG1. The solution must ensure that other objects can be created in RG1.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a lock",
      "B": "an Azure role",
      "C": "a tag",
      "D": "an Azure policy"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #278 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure subscription and 100 Windows 10 devices.\nYou need to ensure that only users whose devices have the latest security patches installed can access Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)-\nintegrated applications.\nWhat should you implement?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a conditional access policy",
      "B": "Azure Bastion",
      "C": "Azure Firewall",
      "D": "Azure Policy"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #279 Topic 1\nWhat can Azure Information Protection encrypt?",
    "options": {
      "A": "network tra\u0000c",
      "B": "documents and email messages",
      "C": "an Azure Storage account",
      "D": "an Azure SQL database"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #280 Topic 1\nWhat should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
    "options": {
      "A": "the Knowledge Center website",
      "B": "the Advisor blade from the Azure portal",
      "C": "Compliance Manager from the Service Trust Portal",
      "D": "the Solutions blade from the Azure portal"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #282 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure subscription.\nWhere will you \u0000nd details on the personal data collected by Microsoft, how Microsoft uses the data, and what the data is used for?",
    "options": {
      "A": "the Data Protection Addendum",
      "B": "the Microsoft Online Services Terms",
      "C": "the Microsoft Privacy Statement",
      "D": "Azure Security Center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #290 Topic 1\nWhat should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Service Health",
      "B": "Azure Knowledge Center",
      "C": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud",
      "D": "Azure Advisor"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #293 Topic 1\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains resources in several regions.\nYou need to create the Azure resource that must be used to meet the policy requirement.\nWhat should you create?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a read-only lock",
      "B": "an Azure policy",
      "C": "a management group",
      "D": "a reservation"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #294 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nFrom Azure Cloud Shell, you can track your company's regulatory standards and regulations, such as ISO 27001.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed.` If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed.",
      "B": "the Microsoft Cloud Partner Portal",
      "C": "Compliance Manager",
      "D": "the Trust Center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #304 Topic 1\nYour company plans to migrate all on-premises data to Azure.\nYou need to identify whether Azure complies with the company's regional requirements.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "the Knowledge Center",
      "B": "Azure Marketplace",
      "C": "the MyApps portal",
      "D": "the Trust Center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #309 Topic 1\nWhat is guaranteed in an Azure Service Level Agreement (SLA) for virtual machines?",
    "options": {
      "A": "uptime",
      "B": "feature availability",
      "C": "bandwidth",
      "D": "performance"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #311 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Basic support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #312 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Standard support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #313 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Premier support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #314 Topic 1\nYour company plans to request an architectural review of an Azure environment from Microsoft.\nThe company currently has a Basic support plan.\nYou need to recommend a new support plan for the company. The solution must minimize costs.\nWhich support plan should you recommend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Premier",
      "B": "Developer",
      "C": "Professional Direct",
      "D": "Standard"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #316 Topic 1\nWhat is required to use Azure Cost Management?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a Dev/Test subscription",
      "B": "Software Assurance",
      "C": "an Enterprise Agreement (EA)",
      "D": "a pay-as-you-go subscription"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #318 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Professional Direct support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #319 Topic 1\nYour company has a Software Assurance agreement that includes Microsoft SQL Server licenses.\nYou plan to deploy SQL Server on Azure virtual machines.\nWhat should you do to minimize licensing costs for the deployment?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Deallocate the virtual machines during off hours.",
      "B": "Use Azure Hybrid Bene\u0000t.",
      "C": "Con\u0000gure Azure Cost Management budgets.",
      "D": "Use Azure reservations."
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #320 Topic 1\nYour company has 10 departments.\nThe company plans to implement an Azure environment.\nYou need to ensure that each department can use a different payment option for the Azure services it consumes.\nWhat should you create for each department?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a reservation",
      "B": "a subscription",
      "C": "a resource group",
      "D": "a container instance"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #327 Topic 1\nWhich statement accurately describes the Modern Lifecycle Policy for Azure services?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Microsoft provides mainstream support for a service for \u0000ve years.",
      "B": "Microsoft provides a minimum of 12 months' notice before ending support for a service.",
      "C": "After a service is made generally available, Microsoft provides support for the service for a minimum of four years.",
      "D": "When a service is retired, you can purchase extended support for the service for up to \u0000ve years."
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #332 Topic 1\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n Five groups in Azure AD\n 10 public IP addresses\n 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nWhich unused resources should you remove?",
    "options": {
      "A": "the network interfaces",
      "B": "the public IP addresses",
      "C": "the groups",
      "D": "the user accounts"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #337 Topic 1\nWho can use the Azure Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) calculator?",
    "options": {
      "A": "billing readers for an Azure subscription only",
      "B": "owners for an Azure subscription only",
      "C": "anyone",
      "D": "all users who have an account in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) that is linked to an Azure subscription only"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #339 Topic 1\nWhich task can you perform by using Azure Advisor?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Integrate Active Directory and Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).",
      "B": "Estimate the costs of an Azure solution.",
      "C": "Con\u0000rm that Azure subscription security follows best practices.",
      "D": "Evaluate which on-premises resources can be migrated to Azure."
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #341 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure application that uses the services shown in the following table.\nHow should you calculate the composite SLA for the application?",
    "options": {
      "A": "0.999 * 0.9999 = 0.9989001 = 99.89001%",
      "B": "0.999 / 0.9999 = 0.9991 = 99.91%",
      "C": "Max(0.999, 0.9999) = 0.9999 = 99.99%",
      "D": "Min(0.999, 0.9999) = 0.999 = 99.9%"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #348 Topic 1\nYou have 1,000 virtual machines hosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou plan to migrate all the virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription.\nYou need to identify which expenditure model to use for the planned Azure solution.\nWhich expenditure model should you identify?",
    "options": {
      "A": "scalable",
      "B": "operational",
      "C": "elastic",
      "D": "capital"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #351 Topic 1\nWhich Service Level Agreement (SLA) is provided for Azure services in public preview?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Each service de\u0000nes its own SLA",
      "B": "The SLA will be 99%",
      "C": "The SLA will be 1% less than the general availability (GA) SLA",
      "D": "The SLA will be 99.95%"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #355 Topic 1\nWhat is the longest term you can purchase for Azure Reserved VM instances?",
    "options": {
      "A": "one year",
      "B": "\u0000ve years",
      "C": "four years",
      "D": "three years"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #357 Topic 1\nYour company has 10 o\u0000ces. You plan to generate several billing reports from the Azure portal. Each report will contain the Azure resource\nutilization of each o\u0000ce.\nWhich Azure Resource Manager feature should you use before you generate the reports?",
    "options": {
      "A": "tags",
      "B": "templates",
      "C": "locks",
      "D": "policies"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #359 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nIf Microsoft plans to end support for an Azure service that does NOT have a successor service, Microsoft will provide noti\u0000cation at least 12\nmonths before.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed.",
      "B": "6 months",
      "C": "90 days",
      "D": "30 days"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #362 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n Five groups in Azure AD\n 10 public IP addresses\n 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused network interfaces.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #363 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\nFive groups in Azure AD -\n 10 public IP addresses\n 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused public IP addresses.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #364 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n Five groups in Azure AD\n 10 public IP addresses\n 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused user accounts.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #367 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nA support plan solution that gives you best practice information, health status and noti\u0000cations, and 24/7 access to billing information at the\nlowest possible cost is a Standard support plan.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed",
      "B": "Developer",
      "C": "Basic",
      "D": "Premier"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #368 Topic 1\nIn which Azure support plans can you open a new support request?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Premier and Professional Direct only",
      "B": "Premier, Professional Direct, and Standard only",
      "C": "Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, and Developer only",
      "D": "Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, Developer, and Basic"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #369 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nYou can create an Azure support request from support.microsoft.com.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed.` If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed.",
      "B": "the Azure portal",
      "C": "the Knowledge Center",
      "D": "the Security & Compliance admin center"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #370 Topic 1\nNote: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution\nthat might meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct\nsolution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review\nscreen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n Five groups in Azure AD\n 10 public IP addresses\n 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused groups.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Yes",
      "B": "No"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #371 Topic 1\nThis question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nThe Azure Standard support plan is the lowest cost option to receive 24x7 access to support engineers by phone.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select\nthe answer choice that makes the statement correct.",
    "options": {
      "A": "No change is needed",
      "B": "Developer",
      "C": "Basic",
      "D": "Professional Direct"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #374 Topic 1\nYou need to compare a company's cloud usage to industry standard best practices.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Monitor",
      "B": "Azure Service Health",
      "C": "Application Insights in Azure Monitor",
      "D": "Azure Advisor"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #375 Topic 1\nYou need to start Azure Cloud Shell.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "the Azure portal",
      "B": "Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI)",
      "C": "Azure PowerShell",
      "D": "an Azure Resource Manager (ARM) template"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #376 Topic 1\nHow many copies of data are maintained by an Azure Storage account that uses locally-redundant storage (LRS)?",
    "options": {
      "A": "3",
      "B": "4",
      "C": "6",
      "D": "9"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #377 Topic 1\nWhat enables a cloud service to adapt quickly to changing requirements?",
    "options": {
      "A": "high availability",
      "B": "predictability",
      "C": "manageability",
      "D": "agility"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #378 Topic 1\nWhat is an example of vertical scaling in a cloud environment?",
    "options": {
      "A": "adding an additional CPU to an existing Azure virtual machine",
      "B": "adding an additional Azure virtual machine",
      "C": "adding an additional Azure Virtual Desktop session host",
      "D": "adding an additional Azure App Service instance automatically"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #381 Topic 1\nWhat additional resource is required by an Azure virtual machine?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a virtual network",
      "B": "a service endpoint",
      "C": "Azure Firewall",
      "D": "a public IP address"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #383 Topic 1\nHow many copies of data are maintained by an Azure Storage account that uses geo-redundant storage (GRS)?",
    "options": {
      "A": "3",
      "B": "4",
      "C": "6",
      "D": "9"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #384 Topic 1\nWhat is used to grant permission to Azure Virtual Desktop resources?",
    "options": {
      "A": "tags",
      "B": "role-based access control (RBAC) roles",
      "C": "resource groups",
      "D": "application security groups"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #389 Topic 1\nWhich cloud service model minimizes the management responsibility of a customer?",
    "options": {
      "A": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)",
      "B": "platform as a service (PaaS)",
      "C": "software as a service (SaaS)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #398 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure web app.\nYou need to manage the settings of the web app from an iPhone.\nWhat are two Azure management tools that you can use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Windows PowerShell",
      "B": "Azure Cloud Shell",
      "C": "the Azure portal",
      "D": "Azure Storage Explorer"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #401 Topic 1\nWhat should you use to prevent tra\u0000c from an Azure virtual network from being routed to an Azure Storage account via the internet?",
    "options": {
      "A": "a network security group (NSG)",
      "B": "a public endpoint",
      "C": "Azure VPN Gateway",
      "D": "a service endpoint"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #402 Topic 1\nWhich service can replace a resource lock automatically if the lock is removed?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Information Protection (AIP)",
      "B": "Azure Blueprints",
      "C": "Azure Backup",
      "D": "Azure Advisor"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #405 Topic 1\nYou plan to collect and analyze event details for \u0000ve Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to run queries to compare the event details collected from all the virtual machines.\nWhich two tools should you use? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Service Health",
      "B": "Azure Service Bus",
      "C": "Azure Monitor",
      "D": "Azure Advisor",
      "E": "Log Analytics"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #407 Topic 1\nWhat should you use to track the costs of Azure resources?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Quickstart templates",
      "B": "tags",
      "C": "budgets",
      "D": "usage and quotas"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #408 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure subscription.\nYou plan to create a virtual machine.\nWhere will the virtual machine be placed in Azure?",
    "options": {
      "A": "In a storage account",
      "B": "In a resource group",
      "C": "In an administrative unit",
      "D": "In an application group"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #411 Topic 1\nYou plan to reduce ongoing Azure expenditures.\nYou need to identify which factors affect the costs of a resource.\nWhich three factors should you identify? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "the volume of outbound data",
      "B": "the volume of inbound data",
      "C": "the service tier",
      "D": "the Azure region",
      "E": "the type of processed data"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #412 Topic 1\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains several resources.\nYou need to identify which department is responsible for the cost of each resource.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "budgets",
      "B": "alerts",
      "C": "tags"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #420 Topic 1\nYou have on-premises servers that run Windows Server.\nWhat should you implement to manage the servers by using the Azure portal?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)",
      "B": "Azure Arc",
      "C": "Docker",
      "D": "role-based access control (RBAC)"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #423 Topic 1\nYou have a web app that runs in Azure.\nYou need to identify the amount of time it takes for web pages to load in a user's browser.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Monitor alerts",
      "B": "Application Insights in Azure Monitor",
      "C": "Log Analytics",
      "D": "Azure Network Watcher"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #425 Topic 1\nWhat should a desktop application use to interact with Azure and manage resources?",
    "options": {
      "A": "APIs",
      "B": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM) templates",
      "C": "Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI)",
      "D": "Azure Cloud Shell"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #429 Topic 1\nWhich two features or services can be integrated with Azure Monitor? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct answer is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure status",
      "B": "Application Insights",
      "C": "Azure Advisor",
      "D": "Log Analytics",
      "E": "Azure Service Health"
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #430 Topic 1\nWhat provides a uni\u0000ed way to project and manage non-Azure resources in Azure Resource Manager (ARM)?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Migrate",
      "B": "Azure AD Connect",
      "C": "Azure Arc",
      "D": "Azure Front Door"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #433 Topic 1\nYour company has an Azure subscription and three business units.\nYou plan to deploy new resources for each business unit.\nYou need to ensure that the new resources are deployed by using a repeatable and reliable method that applies the same con\u0000gurations to\neach resource.\nWhat should you use?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Azure Policy",
      "B": "Azure Arc",
      "C": "a resource group",
      "D": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM) templates"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #437 Topic 1\nIn the software as a service (SaaS) cloud service, which responsibility is shared between Microsoft and the customer?",
    "options": {
      "A": "identity and directory infrastructure management",
      "B": "application management",
      "C": "information and data management",
      "D": "operating system updates"
    },
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #438 Topic 1\nWhere does Azure Monitor store event data?",
    "options": {
      "A": "an Azure Blob Storage account",
      "B": "Azure Storage Queue",
      "C": "Azure SQL Database",
      "D": "a Log Analytics workspace"
    },
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #443 Topic 1\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con\u0000guration to use to run the script.\nWhich three computers can run the script? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "a computer that runs Windows 11 and has the Azure CLI tools installed",
      "B": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed",
      "C": "a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed",
      "D": "a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell",
      "E": "a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #445 Topic 1\nIn the infrastructure as a service (IaaS) cloud service model, which two components are the responsibility of the cloud service provider? Each\ncorrect answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
    "options": {
      "A": "the con\u0000guration and maintenance of storage",
      "B": "the installation and con\u0000guration of the operating system",
      "C": "maintaining the hardware",
      "D": "the network con\u0000guration",
      "E": "physical security of the datacenter infrastructure"
    },
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Question #450 Topic 1\nYou have an Azure Storage account named storage1.\nYou need to ensure that containers can be created in, but not deleted from, storage1.\nWhat should you do?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Create a ReadOnly lock for storage1.",
      "B": "Create a delete lock for storage1.",
      "C": "Enable container soft delete.",
      "D": "Enable blob soft delete."
    },
    "correct_answer": "B"
  }
]